Gabriel's Inferno: Part III is a romance, drama film directed by Tosca Musk.
The final part of the film adaption of the erotic romance novel Gabriel's Inferno
written by an anonymous Canadian author under the pen name Sylvain Reynard.
Julia Mitchell, played by Melanie Zanetti.
Gabriel Emerson, played by Giulio Berruti.
Simon Talbot, played by Rhett Wellington Ramirez.
Paul Norris, played by James Andrew Fraser.
Christa Peterson, played by Margaux Brooke.
Antonio, played by Pat Asanti.
Gabriel's Inferno is an erotic romance novel by an anonymous
Canadian author under the pen name Sylvain Reynard.
The story was first published in novel format in 2011 by Omnific Publishing, with
further publishing rights to the series being purchased by Berkley Books.
The work was first published on 4 September 2012, along with the
second book in the series, Gabriel's Rapture.
The series has been compared to Fifty Shades of Grey because both originated as Twilight fan fiction, with the International
Business Times reporting that Gabriel's Inferno differs in that it bears "few similarities to the story that inspired it".
The novel was originally published online as a Twilight fan fiction entitled The University of Edward Masen
(Edward Masen being Edward Cullen's human name) under the pen name of Sebastien Robichaud.
Gabriel's Inferno and its sequels appeared on The
New York Times Best Seller list.
A film adaptation was released on the streaming service Passionflix.
The film was cut into three parts; the first part of
the film was released on 29 May 2020.
The tone is emotional.